Cory Pekkala

8702 Dorman Cove, Austin TX 78717 Home: 512-218-4080 Cell: 512-656-6515 pekkalacd@yahoo.com

Summary

A college student pursuing a degree in computer science, intent on becoming a software engineer. Reliable, friendly, and professional with experience to prove it. Driven to exceed company expectations, fulfill customer needs, and continually learn. Enthusiastic, hardworking, personable, and authentic.

Skills

- Mac OS, Windows
- MS Office, SAP NetWeaver
- Superb Communicator and Team Player
- Python, C++, HTML, CSS
- Excellent Multi-tasker and Flexible

Experience

Apple Inc.

August 2015 to Sept. 2016

Order Support Specialist

Austin, TX

Managed blocks and maintained order fulfillment through SAP. Assisted logistics and carriers in product recovery, claims, and shipment/return complications. Provided exceptional customer service outbound calls and emails. Processed inbound request for documents such as invoices (archived and non), shipment labels, return material authorizations (RMAs).

NetSpend Dec. 2016 to Apr. 2017

Partner Services Representative

Austin, TX

Managed relationships with partner associates. Processed bank related transactions for partner clientele. Assisted and advised partner clientele and direct customers with payment and billing processing issues and disputes. Assisted with transaction and account activity with both general and partner end users.

Apple Inc. Mar. 2017 to Dec. 2017

Fraud Prevention Specialist

Austin, TX

Accurately reviewed and analyzed information to ensure a reduced risk of fraud. Maintained customer relationships and appropriately advised the next course of action. Established and recognized patterns from organized sets of data presented through a retail-online interface.

The Home Depot Aug. 2019 to Current

Fulfilment Associate

Austin, TX

Prepared customer orders through multiple channels (BOPIS, BOSS, Will Call, Store to Store, Delivery) including but not limited to picking, staging, and loading orders onto trucks. Operated heavy machinery, not limited to reach trucks, forklifts, and electric ladders in order to process and fulfill orders in a timely manner.

Education

McNeil High School High School Diploma

2012

Round Rock, TX, USA

- Graduated with a 3.1 GPA under the Distinguished Plan. Graduated with 6.0 college credits Was a member of BITS

Austin Community College Computer Science

2018 to Present

Austin, TX, USA

- Member of Computer Science Student Association Scholastic Excellence, 3.789 GPA